nyc.com 2013-05-24

# NYC.com Privacy Policy

#### NYC.com Privacy Policy

As New York City's portal, our goal is to offer the best of the city in one convenient site while maintaining a total commitment to your privacy needs and expectations. Please read on for details about our privacy policy. 

#### What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This privacy policy pertains to the use of the NYC.com web site found at both <http://www.nyc.com/> and <http://www.newyorkcity.com/>
  * This privacy policy covers how NYC.com treats personal information that NYC.com collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number.
  * Children under 13 are not permitted to use the NYC.com service, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site.

#### Information Collection and How it is used

#### General Information

  * NYC.com collects personal information when you register with us to use our services or to post content on NYC.com.
  * When you register we ask for your email address and certain optional information such as your name, birth date, birth place, gender, biographical information, ICQ/AIM/Yahoo/MSN user name, and personal interests.
  * For certain products we offer, such as enhanced email accounts, we will ask for your billing address, phone number, and credit card information.
  * NYC.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request.
  * NYC.com uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting.

#### IP Addresses

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in our user registration databases when you register with NYC.com. 

IP addresses may be used for various purposes, including: 

  * To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.
  * To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.
  * To estimate the total number of users visiting NYC.com from specific geographical regions.
  * To make sure that people are not voting for themselves or friends during contests or promotions.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

  * You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.
  * If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use NYC.com products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of the NYC.com service.
  * NYC.com uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:
    * Access your information when you "sign in".
    * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using our services.
    * Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on NYC.com.
    * Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.
    * Conduct research to improve NYC.com content and services.
  * NYC.com lets other companies (such as Google) that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * When you post a message, your NYC.com ID or alias that you are posting under is visible to other users.
  * NYC.com does not rent or sell your personal information. However, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 
  * Generally, NYC.com does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except to provide products or services you've requested and in the following circumstances:
    * NYC.com may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of NYC.com terms of use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. We will transfer information about you if NYC.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, NYC.com will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the NYC.com web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. NYC.com may share demographic information with business partners, such as "53% of users who regularly user NYC.com Blogs are between 18 and 24" or the like. NO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WILL EVER BE USED WITHOUT YOUR PERMISSION.
  * Sweepstakes and Other Promotions. From time to time, we may offer sweepstakes or other promotions involving marketing or advertising partners. If you choose to participate in one of these sweepstakes or promotions, you'll have to provide some information about yourself (such as your name, address, and email address). We may share this information with sponsors of the contest or other promotional partners in order to contact you and to award a prize. We don't control these third parties' privacy practices, and our Privacy Policy does not apply to their collection and use of your information. If you don't want us to collect the information requested in connection with a promotion, or to provide it to our co-sponsors or partners, please do not participate in the promotion. If you have provided us with contact information on a sweepstakes form, you will receive weekly emails from us with updates on the sweepstakes and/or special offers. If you do not want to receive information in the future please, you may opt out at anytime by using the safe unsubscribe feature found in any email we send or by sending us an e-mail to [remove@nyc.com](mailto:remove@nyc.com) with "Remove from List" written in the subject line. 
  * NYC.com displays targeted advertisements based on information that is exhibited in people's profiles.

#### Editing and Deleting Account Information. Security.

  * You can change your NYC.com Account Information, at any time.
  * We may send you certain communications relating to the NYC.com service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, that are considered part of your NYC.com account.
  * You can delete your NYC.com account at any time from your account page; however, please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in NYC.com's records for some period.
  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * Your NYC.com Account Information is password-protected.
  * In certain areas, NYC.com uses SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

NYC.com may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your NYC.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

If you have questions or suggestions please use you the help form or you can contact us at: 

NewYorkCity.com, Inc.  
515 Greenwich St, Fifth Floor Suite 502  
New York, NY 10013
